[{"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_comment2"}],"languages":"python","title":"python course","modules":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"Mock test Question 1(course1,module1,about for loop)","options":["Simulated answer 1","Simulated answer 2","Simulated answer 3","Simulated answer 4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Mock test Question 2(course1,module1,about for loop)","options":["Simulated answer 1","Simulated answer 2","Simulated answer 3","Simulated answer 4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"Mock test Question 3(course1,module1,about for loop)","options":["Simulated answer 1","Simulated answer 2","Simulated answer 3","Simulated answer 4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"while loop question","options":["answer1","answer2","answer3","answer4"],"correctAnswer":2}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 16:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"Scout","lastName":"Solace","password":"123456","userName":"Scout Solace","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"hjfhjdvbbshvgerhjhvyvbherayvgahbjsfsvgfch bndfvhdvgchb fvnhcb xvnbhnfvhuyhfd"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 16:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"Scout","lastName":"Solace","password":"123456","userName":"Scout Solace","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"content"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"loop module","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"for cycle course module 1 Record the class content.","name":"for cycle course module 1 period"},{"lessonContent":"for cycle course module 2 Record the class content.","name":"for cycle course module 2 period"},{"lessonContent":"while loop lesson content","name":"while loop lessnon name"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module2_question1","options":["course1_module2_question1_options1","course1_module2_question1_options2","course1_module2_question1_options3","course1_module2_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module2_question2","options":["course1_module2_question2_options1","course1_module2_question2_options2","course1_module2_question2_options3","course1_module2_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module2_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module2_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module2_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module2_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module2_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module2_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module1_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module2_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module2_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module2_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module2_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module2_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module3_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module4_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module5_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module6_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module7_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module8_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course1_module1_question1","options":["course1_module1_question1_options1","course1_module1_question1_options2","course1_module1_question1_options3","course1_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course1_module1_question2","options":["course1_module1_question2_options1","course1_module1_question2_options2","course1_module1_question2_options3","course1_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course1_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course1_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course1_module9_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course1_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course1_module1_lesson_name2"}]}]},{"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course2_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course2_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_comment2"}],"languages":"python","title":"javaScript course","modules":[{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course2_module1_question1","options":["course2_module1_question1_options1","course2_module1_question1_options2","course2_module1_question1_options3","course2_module1_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course2_module1_question2","options":["course2_module1_question2_options1","course2_module1_question2_options2","course2_module1_question2_options3","course2_module1_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module1_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course2_module1_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module1_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module1_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course2_module1_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module1_comment2"}],"name":"course2_module1_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course2_module1_lesson_content1","name":"course2_module1_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course2_module1_lesson_content2","name":"course2_module1_lesson_name2"}]},{"quiz":{"questions":[{"question":"course2_module2_question1","options":["course2_module2_question1_options1","course2_module2_question1_options2","course2_module2_question1_options3","course2_module2_question1_options4"],"correctAnswer":1},{"question":"course2_module2_question2","options":["course2_module2_question2_options1","course2_module2_question2_options2","course2_module2_question2_options3","course2_module2_question2_options4"],"correctAnswer":1}]},"comments":[{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module2_replies1_comment1"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course2_module2_replies2_comment1"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module2_comment1"},{"replies":[{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module2_replies1_comment2"},{"replies":[],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn2","lastName":"ln2","password":"pas2","userName":"un2","type":"student","email":"ema2"},"comment":"course2_module2_replies2_comment2"}],"author":{"birthday":"Sat Feb 25 02:00:00 CST 2023","firstName":"fn1","lastName":"ln1","password":"pas1","userName":"un1","type":"student","email":"ema1"},"comment":"course2_module2_comment2"}],"name":"course2_module2_name1","lessons":[{"lessonContent":"course2_module2_lesson_content1","name":"course2_module2_lesson_name1"},{"lessonContent":"course2_module2_lesson_content2","name":"course2_module2_lesson_name2"}]}]}]